

Kharitonov Ivan

Male, 25 years, born on 1 November 1991

+7 (916) 7857111 — mobile phone

ipkharitonov@gmail.com — preferred means of communication

Reside in: Moscow, m. VDNKh

Citizenship: Russia, work permit at: Russia

Not ready to relocate, ready for rare business trips

Desired position and salary

Software Engineer/Analyst

Science, Education

• Computer Science, Information Systems Employment: full time, part time, project work

Work schedule: full day

Desired travel time to work: any

Work experience — 8 years 1 month

September 2015 till now 1 year 9 months

FSUE NAMI

Moscow, nami.ru/en/

Software engineer

Information and Intelligent Systems Centre - Transmission Control System Department

- Develop and test basic layer software for sensors and control signals
- Develop plant models and control systems (open loop, close loop and adaptation using ML approach)
- Calibration parameters of control system

Deal with: C, MATLAB, Simulink (Embedded Coder), Python (SciPy, NumPy, ML frameworks), Vector applications for debug and calibration, Altium Designer

March 2013 — August 2015 2 years 6 months

FSAE Bauman racing team

Moscow, www.baumanracing.ru/

Engineer/electrician

Electronic Department

Participation in international engineering competitions as a member of the racing team of the university.

Responsibilities:

- Develop hardware and software for race car
- Participiate in the assembly of vehicle harness
- Organization of joint events with sponsors

Achievements:

- Project presentation of the electronics systems to the judge with positive feedback
- Developed race steering wheel with LCD and elements for control
- Developed straingauge amplifier
- Developed wireless telemetry module for data acquisition
- Established contacts with 3 sponsors

Deal with:

- Solidworks, Altium Designer, STM32, Motec ECU, RTKLIB, LabView, National Instruments devices

February 2012 — June 2013 1 year 5 months

Crypto LLC

Moscow

Engineer

System Integration Department

The company's activity is the software development for digital TV providers. I worked since the establishment of the company.

Responsibilities:

- Testing of the conditional access system with standard DVB SimulCrypt
- Installation and configuration of the system
- Communication with TV equipment vendors

Achievements:

- Development of solutions to adapt the product to the customer (the use of virtualization technologies, fault tolerance KVM, HeartBeat)
- Integration with Zabbix data management system for monitoring

Deal with:

- Project documentation, Linux, SQL, VmWare, KVM, Zabbix

May 2009 — February 2012 2 years 10 months

Dominanta LLC

Moscow, habrahabr.ru/company/beeline/blog/159729/

Monitoring specialist

The company provides television broadcasting for mobile devices in the standard DVB-H.

- # Network maintenance department
- 3 month traineeship
- Get acquainted with the DVB technology and equipment of base and head stations
- # Network monitoring department

Responsibilities:

- Monitoring of the operation of the head and base TV stations
- Work with Rohde & Schwarz professional test and measurement TV equipment
- 2nd level technical support

Education

Higher

2014

2017 Moscow Bauman State Technical University, Moscow

Faculty of Power Engineering, Piston engines

Moscow Bauman State Technical University, Moscow

Faculty of Radioelectronics and Laser Technology (RL), Radioelectronic Systems and Devices

Key skills

Languages

Russian — native

English — I can attend an interview

Skills LabVIEW Python SolidWorks Negotiation skills MATLAB Simulink

Data Analysis Analytical skills Machine Learning English

Project management

Further information

Recommendations Research and Educational Centre "Formula Student"

Onishchenko Dmitry (director)

About me

I have been graduated Bauman MSTU. My specialization is radar systems. From the first year of education, i worked in telecom industry. At university i was interested in GNNS systems and math statistics. Since 2013, I was participated in a student project to build a race car - "Formula Student". In my diploma work described precise RTK positioning and telemetry system of a racecar. Now i am interesting in machine learning and attemt at different competitions. Also i attend ML course (Data mining in action - MIPT).

As for my hobbies, I am fond of karting and motorsport engineering.